NAME IDEAS:
	Blue Husky Open Auto Update Standard (BH-OAUS, /bi-etʃ wɒ́s/)
	Blue Husky Open Standard for Automatic Updates (BH-OSfAU, /bi-etʃ ɒ́s-faw/)
	The Blue Update Standard
	The Huskdate Standard

MAJOR GOALS:
1: To end, once and for all, dialogs that say "click here to go to our website to download the latest version"
2: To make it easier for developers to implement internal updaters, with optional automation
3: To make it possible (or easier, depending on tech prowess) for users to manually check for updates without the aid of the program in question

RANDOM THOUGHTS:
- Use JSON on the server side to transmit data about possible updates
- Use the HTTP(S) and (S)FTP protocols
